Privacy Policy
==============

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any information when you use CryptoTab Browser. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

We respect your privacy and work hard to ensure that we only ever receive the minimum amount of information needed to support the features you’re using. We meticulously protect all the information that we receive.

Types of data collected
-----------------------

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

* First name and last name
* Email address
* Cookies and log data

Use of data
-----------

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.  
In certain circumstances, we may use your Personal Data to contact you regarding your account security and verification.

Log data
--------

We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit CryptoTab Browser ("Log data"). This Log data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

Cookies
-------

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive.We use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Your rights
-----------

We aim to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data. Whenever made possible, you can update your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to change your Personal Data, please contact us to make the required changes by [clicking here](https://cryptobrowser.site/feedback/). Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

Security
--------

We take great care in implementing and maintaining the security of CryptoTab Browser and your information. We employ industry standard procedures and policies to ensure the safety of our users’ information, and prevent unauthorized use of any such information. Although we take reasonable steps to safeguard information, we cannot be responsible for the acts of those who gain unauthorized access or abuse our product, and we make no warranty, express, implied or otherwise, that we will prevent such access.

SSL/TLS encryption
------------------

We use SSL/TLS encryption for security reasons and for the protection of the transmission of confidential content, such as the inquiries you send to us as the site operator. You can recognize an encrypted connection in your browser's address line when it changes from "http://" to "https://" and the lock icon is displayed in your browser's address bar. If SSL or TLS encryption is activated, the data you transfer to us cannot be read by third parties.

Software updates
----------------

Software updates are necessary to keep computers, mobile devices and tablets running smoothly, and to lower security vulnerabilities. The CryptoTab Browser updater is installed alongside with the product as well as the installation process registers a scheduled task. This should help to prevent security issues and improve compatibility and program features. By selecting "Allow automatic updates", you allow updates to be installed automatically by the startup, at the beginning or at the end of the browser session. Otherwise, you will be advised to update our product manually with a separate notification window. The CryptoTab Browser updater is launched as a scheduled task which runs separate process.

Links to other sites
--------------------

Our Service may contain advertising and links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

Changes to this Privacy Policy
------------------------------

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [info@cryptobrowser.site](mailto:info@cryptobrowser.site).
